Guide to the Eldon Dedini Papers
The Ohio State University Billy Ireland Cartoon Library & Museum
- Series XIII. Memorabilia, 1920s-2000s, Undated
  - Baby Bonnet made for Dedini, 1921 (Box ED 89, Folder 5)
  - Child's Leather Glove, Undated (Box ED 89, Folder 6)
  - Announcement of Dedini's Birth by Grandmother, 1921 (Box ED 89, Folder 7)
  - Cancelled checks to Chouinard Art Institute, 1942-1944 (Box ED 89, Folder 8)
  - "A Record of Our Baby's Life" Dedini's Baby Book, 1920s (Box ED 89, Folder 9)
  - Dedini's Baby Photograph Album, 1920s (Box ED 89, Folder 10)
  - Baby Photograph of Dedini, Undated (Box ED 89, Folder 11)
  - Seaside Jazz Art Show Honoree, Award of Appreciation to Eldon Dedini, 1997 (Box ED 90, Folder 1)
  - National Cartoonists Society Reuben Award, Best Magazine Gag Cartoonist, 1989 (Box ED 90, Folder 2)
  - Clipboard used by Eldon Dedini to draw roughs, Undated (Box ED 91, Folder 1)
  - National Cartoonists Society Reuben Award, Best Magazine Gag Cartoonist, 1961 (Box ED 91, Folder 2)
  - Thank You from Room 4 Booklet, Undated (Box ED 91, Folder 3)
  - Dedini Family Tree Chart, Undated (Box ED 92, Folder 1)
  - Local Newspaper Clippings about Dedini, 1960s-1970s (Box ED 92, Folder 2)
  - King City Union High Class Reunion, 2000 (Box ED 92, Folder 3)
  - "Thank You for Mr. Dedini" booklet from Grade 4, Room 7, Larkin School Monterey, 1979 (Box ED 92, Folder 4)
  - "Certificate for Meritorious Performance and Serving Monterey Far, Far Beyond the Call of Duty", 1969 (Box ED 92, Folder 5)
  - King City Union High School Class Photograph, 1939 (Box ED 92, Folder 6)
  - Eldon Dedini Portrait Photograph, 1949 (Box ED 92, Folder 7)
  - Copy of Dedini Family Photograph, ca.1930s-1940s (Box ED 92, Folder 8)
  - Copy of Group Photograph (Possibly Dedini Ancestors), Undated (Box ED 92, Folder 9)
  - Image of Virginia Conroy and Image of Dedini's first newspaper cartoon in the Salinas Index- Journal on foam core, ca.2000 (Box ED 92, Folder 10)
  - Oversized photostats of Disney animation storyboards, 1940s (Box ED 92, Folder 11)
  - Wine Lables, "Watkins, Pearson, Larsh & Dedini", Undated (Box ED 100, Folder 23)
  - Savvga, Photograph of Wine Label Designed by Eldon Dedini, 2006 (Box ED 100, Folder 24)
  - "Joyful Jottings" Scrapbook, Undated (Box ED 100, Folder 25)
  - Piano Recital Program, 1935 (Box ED 100, Folder 26)